("That's Entertainment")
(soft rock music)
♪ A police car and a screaming siren ♪
♪ A pneumatic drill and
ripped up concrete ♪
♪ A baby wailing and stray dog howling ♪
♪ The screech of brakes
and lamp light blinking ♪
♪ That's entertainment ♪
♪ A smash of glass and
the rumble of boots ♪
♪ An electric train and
a ripped up phone booth ♪
♪ Paint splattered walls
and the cry of a tomcat ♪
♪ Lights going out and
a kick in the balls ♪
♪ I tell ya that's entertainment ♪
♪ That's entertainment ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Fa la la la la ♪
♪ Days of speed and slow time Monday's ♪
♪ Pissing down with rain
on a boring Wednesday ♪
♪ Watching the news and
not eating your tea ♪
♪ A freezing cold flat
and damp on the walls ♪
♪ I say that's entertainment ♪
♪ That's entertainment ♪
♪ Waking up at 6 a.m.
on a cool warm morning ♪
♪ Opening the windows
and breathing in petrol ♪
♪ An amateur band rehearsing
in a nearby yard ♪
♪ Watching the tele and
thinking about your holidays ♪
♪ That's entertainment,
that's entertainment ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Waking up from bad dreams
and smoking cigarettes ♪
♪ Cuddling a warm girl and
smelling stale perfume ♪
♪ A hot summer's day and
sticky black tarmac ♪
♪ Feeding ducks in the park
and wishing you were far away ♪
♪ That's entertainment,
that's entertainment ♪
♪ Two lovers kissing amongst
the scream of midnight ♪
♪ Two lovers missing the
tranquility of solitude ♪
♪ Getting a cab and traveling on buses ♪
♪ Reading the graffiti
about slashed seat affairs ♪
♪ I tell ya that's entertainment,
that's entertainment ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ La la la la la la ♪